A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1972-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 32692], 1982-1986, Extent: 17 cu. ft. (17 boxes). (Box 1-17)
  - General files, Cabinet, Transportation, Sec. of (Fogarty), 1982 (Box 2)
  - General files, Agriculture, Dept. of, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Attorney General, General correspondence (REVIEW), 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Civil Digest, The, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Freedom of Information, Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, New Program Initiatives, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Budget, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Budget presentations, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Budget process, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Addendum to the budget, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Budget process (Social Services; Aging; Children; Health Serv. Cost Rev. Comm; Women Comm.; Deaf, Health), 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Budget process (MHMRS; Rehab. Center for Blind; Rehab. Services; Visually Handicapped; Volunteerism; WWRC; St. Advocacy Office), 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - General files, Accounts, Dept. of, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, State Board of Elections, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Employee Relations Counselors, Office of, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Hazardous chemicals, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Other state agencies, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Environment, Council on the, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, General Services, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Corrections, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Crime Commission, Virginia State, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Education, Dept. of, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Highways and Transportation, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Housing and Community Development, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, EEO Program, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Personnel and Training, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Telecommunications, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Virginia State Library, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, MASD, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, "Missed Opportunities Report," 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Small Farm Dev. Group Report, VSU, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Capital Budget Tour, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, Planning and Development, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, DPS, "Duplication and Undue Competition Study," 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - General files, UVA, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, UVA, C. Darden Graduate School, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, VRRS, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, VCU, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, Va. Tech, Center for Gerontology, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, Water Control Board, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, General Assembly, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, House Document 43, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, HJR 27, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, HJR 76-77, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, HJR 77, 1983 (Box 5)
  - General files, HJR 87, 1982 (Box 5)
  - General files, HJR 92, 1982 (Box 5)
  - General files, HJR 147, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, SB 10 and HB 110, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, SB 356, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, Prevention of Infant Mortality, 1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, Virginians with Disabilities Act, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, HB 817, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, SJR 42, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - General files, Legislation, 1985 (Box 6)
  - General files, SB 81, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, JLARC File 1-2, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Division of Legislative Services, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, House Appropriations Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Legislative Impact Statements, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Senate Finance Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Senate Correspondence, 1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, GA Testimony, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Advisory Commission on Small Business, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Task Force for the War on Drugs, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Economic Advisory Council, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Governor's Coal and Energy Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Governor's Local Government Advisory Council, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Council on Physical Fitness, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Alcohol and Drug Abuse Problems, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Alcohol and Drug Abuse Advisory Council, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Child Abuse and Neglect Advisory Council, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Task Force on Drunk Driving, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Child Support Enforcement Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Committee on the Future, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Migrant Farmworkers on Virginia Eastern Shore, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Solid Waste Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Governor's Regulatory Reform Advisory Board, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Overall Advisory Council on the Needs of Handicapped Persons, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Task Force on Science and Technology, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Toxic Substance Advisory Council, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Uranium Advisory Group, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Virginia Voluntary Formulary Board, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Social Services block grants, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Block grants meeting minutes and correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Commission on Block grants, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
  - General files, Social Services Block grants, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Social Services Low Income Energy Assistance Grant, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Social Services, Drug abuse and MH Service, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Congress, Miscellaneous correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, U.S. Congress, Office of Technology, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Governor, Cabinet Study, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Governor, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Governor, Fellows, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Governor, Invitations and acknowledgements, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Governor, Miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Governor, Press releases, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, Washington Liaison Office, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - General files, "Staffing and Methods Study," 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Capital Project requests, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Governor's speeches, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Executive Order 47, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Transition issues, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Lieutenant Governor, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Condition on the Commonwealth, 1983 (Box 9)
  - General files, Social Services, Family Violence Prevention Program, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Aircrafts, State owned, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Appalachian Regulatory Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Association for Retarded Citizens, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Executive Summary, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Car Pool Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Five Year Report on CenTeX Operations, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Center for Natural Resources Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Coal Slurry Pipelines, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Council of State Governments, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Office for Civil Rights, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, U.S. Dept. of Education, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, E.P.A., 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Dept. of Energy, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Virginia State Fair, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - General files, Federal Executive Institute, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, Human Service Institute, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, "Low Level Radioactive Waste," 1983 (Box 10)
  - General files, National Governor's Association, Opinion Report, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, National Governor's Association, Legisline, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, National Governor's Association, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, National Center for Health Services Research, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, Nurses Association, Virginia nursing, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - General files, OMB Circular A-122 and A-95, 1983 (Box 10)
  - General files, U.S. Savings Bond Campaign, 1985 (Box 11)
  - General files, Southern Governors' Association, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - General files, So. Institute for Human Resources, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, So. Regional Education Board, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Virginia Health Care Association, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Virginia Association of Rehab. Fac., 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Virginia Cares, Inc., 1982 (Box 1)
  - General files, Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Executive Agreements Quarterly Reports, 1985 (Box 1)
  - General files, Visually Handicapped, AAA Program Assessment, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - General files, "Operations and Organizational Working Group for the Center for Innovative Technology," 1983 (Box 1)
  - General files, Professional Serv. and Nes. Activities, 1983 (Box 1)
  - General files, "Migrant Farmworkers on Virginia's Eastern Shore," 1983 (Box 1)
  - General files, "Task Force on Roles and Responsibilities in the Health Prof. Regulatory System," 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 33417], 1983, Extent: 10 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 1-10)
  - VEC, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Executive agreements, 1983 (Box 2)
  - General files, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Agency head employment applications (Review for privacy), 1983 (Box 4)
  - Block grants, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Health, General files, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Medicaid, General files, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Meetings; Conflict of interest; Infant mortality, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 9-10)
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 33719], 1984-1989, Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  - Agency files, Aging, 1986-1988 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Children, Child Care Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Children, Child Care Initiatives, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Deaf, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, 1986-1988 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, JTPA, 1986-1988 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Worker Adjustment Assistance, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Constituent mail, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., General, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Constituent mail, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., General, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Constituent mail, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Asbestos removal, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Cedar Island, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Certificate of Need, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Grants, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Hazardous waste, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Hazardous Materials Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Health Congress, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., King and Queen County Landfill, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Mt. Rogers Dist., 1986 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Task Force on Nursing, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Public Health Nurses, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Nursing Homes, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Surrogate Motherhood, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., WIC Program, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Indigent Health Reports, 1984-1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Health Care Cost, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Indigent Health, Constituent mail, 1985-1988 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Governor's Task Force on Indigent Health Care, 1986-1988 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Indigent Health Care Study, 1986-1988 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Board, 1986-1988 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Board, Constituent mail, 1986-1988 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health Professional Regulatory System, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost Review Council, 1986-1988 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Council on Indians, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, 1986-1988 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Constituent mail, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid (Review for privacy), 1986 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid Constituent mail, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, General, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid Constituent mail, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Manning Convalescent Home, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Constituent mail, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Community Service Boards, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Constituent mail, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, C.A.D.R.E., 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Drug and Alcohol Abuse, 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Central State Hospital, 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Eastern State Hospital, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Northern Virginia Training Center, 1985-1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Southside Virginia Training Center, 1985-1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Western State Hospital, 1985-1987 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Constituent mail, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, EHS Grand Jury Investigation (Review for privacy), 1986 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Adventure Bound School, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Southwestern Virginia Training Center, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, General, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, General, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Rehabilitation Board, 1985-1987 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Head Trauma Program, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Head Injury Council, 1986-1989 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Head Injury Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Traumatic Brain Injury Project, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Sheltered Workshops, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Woodrow Wilson Rehab Center, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Rights of the Disabled, 1985-1988 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, Constituent mail, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, Report, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Care, Constituent mail, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Briefing materials, 1984-1989 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Adult Day Care, 1985-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Community Action, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Fuel Assistance, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Information and Referral System, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, License and Cert. Childrens. Res., 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Licensing Division, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Reorganization, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, Constituent mail, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support (Review for privacy), 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Aid to Dependent Children, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Abuse, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, Constituent mail, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Bloomfield School, 1986 (Box 12)
  - General files, A to Z, Misc., 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Academy of Clinical Psychologists, 1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Administration, Sec. of, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Alcohol and Drug Abuse Problems, Governor's Council on, 1985-1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, American Foundation for the Blind, 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Coalition for the Mentally Disabled, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Commission of Federal Funding, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Commission on Efficiency, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Community Action, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Community Services Boards, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Conflict of Interest, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Congressional Delegation, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Delmarva Rural Ministries, 1984-1989 (Box 13)
  - General files, Education, Sec. of, 1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Family Life Education, 1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Forum on Families, 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, General Assembly, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, House Document 8, 1985 (Box 13)
  - General files, HB 198 (Housing for Disabled), 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, HB 817, 1985 (Box 13)
  - General files, HJR 260 (Drug Abuse), 1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Governor's Office, General, 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Head Injury Foundation, 1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Henrico County, 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Homeless, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Housing, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Immigration Reform Act, Governors Task Force on, 1984-1989 (Box 13)
  - General files, Innovations, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Instructive Visiting Nurse Association, 1987 (Box 13)
  - General files, Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, League of United Latin Americans, 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Organizations, 1984-1989 (Box 13)
  - General files, Plan of Cooperation, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - General files, Prevention Block Grants, 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Refugees 1986 (Box 13)
  - General files, Virginia Health Care Association, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 34301], 1987-1989, Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  - Agency files, Aging, General, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Children, General, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Children, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Council on Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, General, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Council on Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training Dept., General, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training Dept., Dislocated Workers Act, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., General, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., AIDS, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Dept., Health Planning Board, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, General, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost REview Council, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Indians, Council on, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, General, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid constituent mail, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, General, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, General, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Woodrow Wilson Rehab Center, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Rights of the Disabled, General, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Rights of the Disabled, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, Constituent mail, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Volunteerism, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Women, Council on the Status of, 1989 (Box 3)
  - General files, Community Action Agencies, 1989 (Box 3)
  - General files, Head and Spinal Cord Injuries, 1989 (Box 3)
  - General files, Long Term Care Council, 1989 (Box 3)
  - General files, Prevention Council, 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - General files, Refugees, 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - General files, Victims of Crime Act, 1989 (Box 3)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 34553], 1990-1992, Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  - Agency files, Aging, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Aging, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Deaf and Hard of Hearing, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, General, 1990 (Box 1)